ANDREW ANC

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrew-anc-0911721a/

Github: https://github.com/aancjr

Portfolio: https://aancjr.github.io/Master-Portfolio/

Merrimac MA, 01860 Phone: 978.457.5782

Email: andrewaancjr@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Full-stack developer educated at the University of New Hampshire Coding Bootcamp program with experience in front-end and back-end software languages. Organized, curious, focused and detail oriented. Experienced in providing short-term and long-term solutions based on a needs analysis assessment, and being a powerful team contributor. Natural aptitude for technology and problem solving, life-long learner and an excellent communicator.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

Front-End Technologies: Bootstrap, jQuery.

Back-End Technologies: Express, Node, MongoDB, MySQL, Firebase.

Other: Chrome Developer Tools, AJAX, Git.

PROJECTS

bamazon! | Github: https://github.com/aancjr/bamazon

- An Amazon-like storefront application used in the command line to interact with the customer or manager of the store.
- Tools and languages used: node.js, MySQL, JavaScript, NPM Packages (Inquirer, mysql, cli-table3).

Crystal Collector | Github: https://github.com/aancjr/Crystal-Collector

- Web-based game where the user must click the correct sequence of gems to total the computer's guess.
- Tools and languages used: ¡Query, JavaScript, CSS, HTML.

EXPERIENCE

Medical Account Executive	Jan 2019 - Current EBSCO Information Services - Ipswich, MA.
Dealer Relations Manager	July 2018 - December 2018 CarGurus, Inc Cambridge, MA.
SSD Account Executive	Jan 2018 - July 2018 EBSCO Information Services - Ipswich, MA.
Elsevier Account Manager	May 2014 - Jan 2018 EBSCO Information Services - Ipswich, MA.
K-8 Account Executive	Nov 2013 - May 2014 EBSCO Information Services - Ipswich, MA.

Experience Details: My sales career has taught me many life lessons and continues to do so, but a few valuable skills are what have made me the most successful: Communication, creativity, attitude, leadership, and teamwork.

Key Accomplishments:

• 300% Sales Club - Achieved award for exceeding 300% of my annual sales quota.

EDUCATION

Web Development Bootcamp Certificate Bachelor's of Science in Business 2019 | University of New Hampshire - Portsmouth, NH. 2011 | Full Sail University - Winter Park, FL.